All right, it's a new day. That stuff about Rachel?
好了，這是全新的一天 關於瑞秋那件事呢？
You don't feel that now. It was crazy. You're fine. You're better than fine.
現在你沒有感覺，那太瘋了 你沒事，你好的不得了
You are, as your friend Tony would say, "Great!"
沒錯，就像你朋友湯尼說的 「太帥了」
Everything's normal. She's just your friend, Rachel.
一切都很正常 瑞秋她只是你的朋友
Your friend, Rachel. Your friend. Rachel.
你的朋友瑞秋 你的朋友瑞秋
-Hi, sweetie. -Hey, it's your girlfriend, Rachel!
-嗨，甜心 -嗨，她是你女朋友瑞秋
The One Where Chandler Takes A Bath
本集播出：錢德泡澡記
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Are you..? Are you high?
你…你很興奮嗎？
I just had the most amazing bath.
我剛剛泡了一個最舒服的澡
-Really? I don't like baths. -You like them with me.
-真的嗎？我不喜歡泡澡 -你喜歡跟我泡鴛鴦浴
Honey, it's not the bath I enjoy. It's the wet, naked lady.
甜心，我不是喜歡泡澡 我是喜歡看全身濕答答的裸體女人
-Baths are so relaxing. -Really? What do you do?
-泡澡能讓你放鬆 -真的嗎？你在裡面做什麼？
You just sit in there, stewing in your own filth.
你坐在那裡 被自己的髒水泡著
How dirty do you think I am?
你覺得我有多髒呢？
If you had some candles and bubbles and music, you would love it.
如果有蠟燭、泡泡跟音樂
It would take all of your stress away.
你一定會喜歡它的
它會讓你完全地放鬆
It's 2:00 on a Wednesday and I'm watching Road Rules.
現在是星期三兩點 我正在看越野單車賽
How stressed do you think I am?
你覺得我的壓力會有多大
Hey, Chandler. You got a minute? I really need to talk to you.
錢德，你有空嗎？ 我真的需要跟你談一談
Oh, yeah. Is this a cold-pizza talk or a leftover-meat loaf talk?
對，這是冷披薩談話 還是烤肉剩菜談話？
Well, neither.
都不是
Oh, my God, what's up?
天啊，發生了什麼事？
I don't know. It's just..
我不知道，那只是…
Lately, I've been feeling..
最近我覺得…
Okay, here's what it is.
好吧，事情是這樣的
You know what? I feel a lot better. Thanks.
你知道嗎？ 我覺得好多了，謝謝
No. Come back here and talk to me, mon frere.
不，快回來告訴我 猶豫先生
-Who? -Just come back.
-誰？ -回來吧
Okay.
好吧
You and Monica, friends for a long time.
你跟摩妮卡 當了很久的朋友
And sure, there are rules. But then you went to London.
當然這是有規則的 之後你們去了倫敦
But that's different. There are rules there too, you know what I mean?
但那不一樣，這也是有規則的 你瞭解我的意思嗎？
Do you?
是嗎？
It was different for you guys. You were both in the same place, right?
對你們來說是不一樣的 你們剛好去了同一個地方，對吧？
-In London? -Yeah.
-在倫敦？ -對
Yes, when Monica and I were in London, we were both in London.
對，摩妮卡跟我在倫敦時 我們剛好都在那裡
You know what. This is a bad idea. Forget all about it.
你知道嗎？這是個爛主意 算了
And listen, do me a favor, this conversation between you and me.
聽著，幫我一個忙 別把這件事說出去
If that.
我會盡力的
（中央咖啡廳）
How do I keep losing at tic-tac-toe?
為什麼我玩井字棋老是會輸呢？
Oh, no, no, honey. My circle always stays in the middle.
不，甜心 我的圈圈一直都停留在中間
Oh, Ross, don't forget we have that doctor's appointment tomorrow.
羅斯，別忘了 明天我們要一起去產檢
-To find out the sex of the baby? -No. We don't wanna know.
-你們要知道寶寶的性別？ -不，我們不想知道
All we care about is that it's happy and healthy.
我們只在乎 寶寶是不是健康快樂
Yep, happy and healthy. And cute.
對，健康快樂，還有可愛
-And smart. With an aptitude for science. -Popular.
-跟聰明，還要有科學精神 -受歡迎
Are you two talking about the same baby?
你們兩個說的是 同一個寶寶嗎？
-Hey, have you thought of names? -Oh, yeah. I've come up with a bunch.
-你們想到名字了嗎？ -對，我想到一大堆
-Really? Me too. -Me too.
-真的嗎？我也是 -我也是
Really?
真的？
If it's a girl, Phoebe. And if it's a boy, Pheebo.
如果是女孩就叫菲比 如果是男孩就叫菲寶
Maybe. But it wouldn't hurt to have a backup, you know?
或許吧，但想些備用名字 應該無傷大雅
-Rach, what were you thinking? -Okay.
-瑞秋，你想到什麼名字？ -好吧
I was thinking if it's a girl..
我想如果是女孩
how about Sandrene? It's French.
叫她珊德妮好嗎？那是法文
That's a really pretty name for an industrial solvent.
那很適合化學溶劑公司
-Okay, fine. What do you have? -It's for a boy.
-好吧，你想到什麼？ -我想到男生的名字
I know it's a little out there, but..
我知道那沒有什麼，但是…
Darwin.
達爾文
Oh, my God. Our child will be beaten to death in the schoolyard.
天啊，我們的孩子 會在操場上被打死
Yeah, by Sandrene.
對，被珊德妮打死
You're saying that because I said no to your name.
你會那麼說 因為我不喜歡你想的名字
I'm really, really not.
我真的沒有
How about you each get five vetoes?
你們何不各想五個名字？
-That sounds fair. -I don't think you'll need it. Check this out.
-聽起來很公平 -我想你不需要，聽著
If it's a girl, Rain.
如果是女孩就叫做小雨
-Veto. -Why?
-否決 -為什麼？
Rain? "Hi, my name is Rain.
小雨？嗨，我叫小雨
I have my own kiln, and my dress is made out of wheat."
我有自己的爐子 我的衣服是用麥子做的
I know her!
我認識她
I bought a homemade soap from her at a Dead show!
我在死人表演裡 跟她買了一塊手工肥皂
-Okay. How about for a guy, Thatcher? -Why do you hate our child?
-好，如果是女孩就叫她柴契爾 -你為什麼那麼恨我們的孩子？
-Fine, you go. -Okay. James.
-好吧，輪到你了 -詹姆斯
-But only if it's a girl. -Veto.
-但我可能生的是女孩 -否決
I like Ruth. What about Ruth?
我喜歡蘿絲，你覺得呢？
Oh, I'm sorry. Are we having an 89-year-old?
抱歉 我們要生下89歲的寶寶？
-How about Dayton? -Veto. Stewart.
-戴頓呢？ -否決，史都華
Veto. Sawyer.
否決，莎耶
-Veto. Helen. -Veto.
-否決，海倫 -否決
Is it me, or is Veto starting to sound really good?
是我想歪了 還是否決會是個好名字？
Boy, do I have a surprise for you.
天啊，我為你準備了一個大驚喜
Sex on the balcony?
我們要在陽台上做愛？
No. But someone's not gonna get over that idea.
不，但有個人 忘不了那個想法
-What is it? -I drew you a bath.
-怎麼了？ -我幫你放了洗澡水
I don't like baths. Could you draw me a picture of us having sex on the balcony?
我不喜歡洗澡 你願意跟我去陽台上做愛嗎？
Please. Will you just try it for me. I used all my best stuff.
拜託你試試看 我使出了全身解數
I lit candles, I put on music. I used bath salts, plus bubble bath.
我點了蠟燭，放了音樂 用了浴鹽跟泡泡澡
And got you this little plastic Navy ship! So it's a boy bath.
我還幫你找到海軍模型船 這是男人會洗的澡
-This does butch it up a bit. -I swear, if you try it, you will love it.
-這稍微有點男人味 -我發誓你試過後一定會愛上它
If I do this, can we at least discuss sex on the balcony?
如果我這麼做 我們能不能討論在陽台上做愛的事？
Absolutely.
當然可以
But I know how that discussion's gonna go.
但我知道 我們會怎麼討論它
All right, this isn't so bad. I like the flowery smell.
好吧，這還不賴 我喜歡花香味
Which is okay, because I've got my boat.
沒關係 因為我有我的船
I can actually feel my tension just melting away.
我可以感覺到 壓力消除了
I could fall asleep in here.
我快睡著了
I could drown in here.
我可能會被淹死
Drowning.
我快淹死了
-So? -Oh, my God.
-怎麼樣？ -我的天啊
I told you you were a bath person. Hey, maybe I can give you a facial.
我說過你會喜歡洗澡 或許我可以幫你做臉
I'm gonna need a bigger boat.
我需要大一點的船
I don't think you had an open mind about the name Ruth.
我覺得你對蘿絲這個名字 沒有抱著開闊的胸襟
I mean, come on, little Ruthie Geller? How cute is that?
拜託嘛，小蘿絲蓋勒 可愛吧？
Oh, my God, I can practically hear the mahjong tiles.
天啊 我可以聽到麻將聲
Okay. All your tests look fine. Are you interested in knowing the sex of the baby?
好了，檢查結果都很正常 你們想知道寶寶的性別嗎？
-No, we're not. -But you have it right there in that file?
-我們不想知道 -但病歷裡面有記錄？
You could tell us whether it's a boy or a girl?
你可以告訴我們 是男孩或是女孩？
Dayton or Sandrene? Phoebe or Pheebo?
戴頓或珊德妮？ 菲比或菲寶？
That's right. But if you don't wanna know..
沒錯 如果你們不想知道
-No, we wanna wait. Right? -Right. Right.
-不，我們要等，對吧？ -對
Oh, I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
I know it's really not my place..
我知道我不該那麼說
but please don't name your child Pheebo.
但請不要將你們的寶寶 取名為菲寶
So which of these babies do you think is the ugliest?
你覺得哪個寶寶最醜？
What? Rach, come on, that's terrible.
什麼？瑞秋，那太可怕了
They're babies. They're all beautiful.
他們是寶寶 他們都很可愛
-Third one from the left? -Yeah. Why is it staring at me?
-左邊數過來第三個？ -對，它為什麼要盯著我看？
I think it knows I'm talking about it. Don't you..? You're looking!
我想它知道我在說它 你不…你在偷看
-I didn't! -I saw you!
-我沒有 -我看到了
Fine, I did, but I didn't see anything.
好吧，我在偷看 但我什麼都沒有看到
Shame on you! Ugly baby judges you!
你太可恥了，丑寶寶唾棄你
-Okay. But listen to me, I didn't.. -Don't tell me! I don't wanna know!
-好吧，聽我說，我沒有… -別告訴我，我不想知道
I couldn't even if I wanted to, because I don't know!
我想說也沒辦法說 因為我不知道
I swear I didn't see anything! I don't want to know. It was just a momentary lapse.
我發誓我什麼都沒看到，我不想知道 剛剛我是一時糊塗
Momentary lapse? Don't you have any self-control?
一時糊塗？ 你不懂得自製嗎？
Okay. A couple months late on the lecture, Ross.
好吧，現在跟我說教 已經遲了好幾個月，羅斯
Hello?
哈囉
I'm in the bathroom. Can you come in here? I think there's something wrong.
我在浴室，你能進來一下嗎？ 我覺得不太對勁
You know what? I think I'll wait out here.
你知道嗎？ 我在這裡等
I'm in the bathtub.
我在浴缸裡
-What's wrong? -I drew my own bath, but I did it wrong.
-怎麼了？ -我自己放洗澡水，但我沒有弄對
The water's tepid, the salt didn't dissolve and is now lodged places.
水溫溫的，浴鹽無法溶解 現在它們結塊了
And the scents I used don't compliment each other. Eucalyptus and chamomile?
我用的香味聞起來很不協調 尤加利樹跟甘菊？
-What? -Bath salts.
-什麼？ -浴鹽
They're starting to effervesce.
它們開始冒泡了
It's different.
感覺完全不同
It's interesting.
這真的很有趣
Okay. Let's talk about something else.
好吧，我們談談別的事
Yeah. Sure. So, what was going on with you today?
當然 今天你過得還好吧？
I actually had the weirdest conversation with Joey.
我跟喬伊 談了一件很奇怪的事
He was talking about rules and right and wrong.
他談到規則及對錯
-I had the same conversation. -You did? What was he talking about?
-我也跟他談過 -是嗎？他到底在說什麼？
He hasn't had this much trouble getting out words since we saw him in Macbeth.
自從他演過馬克白後 我還沒看過他說不出話的樣子
That was a long night.
那是漫長的一夜
All right, let's break this down. What exactly did he say to you?
好吧，我們來談談這件事 他到底跟你說了什麼？
He was talking about rules and looking at people differently.
他說到規則 對別人有不同的看法
-He didn't say that to me. -What'd he tell you?
-他沒有跟我說那個 -他跟你說了什麼？
He was asking questions about you, me and London.
他問到你跟我 在倫敦發生的事
And the glue that holds this all together, the rules.
我們是怎麼開始的 還有規則
Okay. So you, me and London.
好吧，你跟我在倫敦
Looking at people differently.
對別人有不同的看法
Maybe he wants to do what you and I did in London with someone.
或許他想跟某人 發生你跟我在倫敦發生的事
But what'd he mean by "rules"?
但他說「規則」是什麼意思？
Wait. He stopped talking the minute Phoebe came in.
等一下，菲比走進來時 他就不說了
-Because he was looking at her differently. -And Phoebe is his friend.
-因為他用不同的眼光看她 -菲比是他的朋友
So he thinks that would be breaking the rules.
他覺得那違反了規則
My God, he wants to do it with Phoebe in London!
天啊，他想跟菲比在倫敦上床
-You guys? -Just a minute!
-你們在哪裡？ -等一下
-That's Mrs. Tribbiani. -You don't say anything.
-崔比亞尼太太來了 -什麼都別說
Why would I say anything?
我為什麼要說？
That two of our friends could start the greatest love affair of their lives?
我們的兩個好朋友 要真正地談戀愛？
They would have me to thank. Then we could all start having babies!
他們會謝謝我 然後我們可以開始做寶寶
-I'm not gonna let you say anything. -You just stay here.
-我不要你告訴她 -你待在這裡
Oh, God!
天啊
Hey, Monica, I brought back your iron.
摩妮卡，我拿熨斗來還你
Oh, you had that? I thought I lost it. I got a new one a month ago.
是你把它拿走的？我以為我弄丟了它 一個月前我買了一個新的
Oh, just as well. I broke this one.
太好了，我把它弄壞了
-What? -Nothing.
-什麼？ -沒事
Okay.
好吧
I really shouldn't say. I'm really not supposed to.
我真的不該說 我不應該說出來的
Fine.
好吧
It's a humdinger.
這是個好消息
Well, then it's really too bad that you can't tell me.
可惜你不能告訴我
Somebody likes you!
有人喜歡你
Is it Chandler?
是錢德嗎？
-No! -Then tell him to stop staring.
-不 -叫他別再盯著我看
It's Joey.
是喬伊
Really? Joey? You don't say.
真的嗎？喬伊？你騙人
-Is it something you'd be interested in? -I don't know, I don't know.
-你會有興趣嗎？ -我不知道
You know, I mean, on the one hand, "Mother, may I?"
我是說 一方面 我在想 「天啊，我可以嗎？」
But, you know, on the other hand..
但在另一方面
No. No, I can't. We're friends.
不行，我們是朋友
Oh, no. I don't wanna risk what we have.
不，我不能冒險 失去我們現在的友誼
I guess that makes sense. You think you're gonna talk to him?
我猜你說的對 你會跟他談一談嗎？
Sure. I mean, it's Joey. I don't want him to get hurt.
當然，他是喬伊 我不希望他受傷害
Well, I must say, I am on fire! First Chandler, now Joey.
我得說我真的很辣 先是錢德，現在又是喬伊
-Not Chandler. Just Joey. -Sure.
-沒有錢德，只有喬伊 -當然
You know what? I've been thinking about it. I'm coming around on the name Ruth.
你知道嗎？我想過了 我接受蘿絲這個名字
I think I would actually consider naming our child that.
我可以考慮 幫孩子取那個名字
Rach, I can't tell you how much that means to me.
瑞秋，我無法告訴你 這對我來說意義有多麼重大
Wait a minute.
等一下
Wait a minute. You hated the name Ruth. Why would you change your mind?
等一下，你討厭蘿絲這個名字 你為什麼會改變心意？
Unless you know we're never gonna have to use it.
除非你知道 我們用不著它
You did see. You know it's a boy!
你看到了，你知道寶寶是男孩
I didn't see anything. I actually changed my mind about the name.
我什麼都沒有看到 我真的是改變了心意
I don't think so. You're giving me Ruth..
我不那麼認為 你答應讓我選蘿絲
so you get to name him when it's a boy.
如果你生了兒子 你可以幫他取名字
That's when you'll swoop in and name him Heath or Blaine or Sequoia.
那時候你會決定叫他 海瑟，布蘭恩或史奎亞
I would.. Sequoia!
我會…史奎亞
-Veto. -Fine.
-否決 -好吧
Unless..
除非…
you anticipated that I would figure all this out..
你知道我會看穿你的陰謀
and you know that it actually is a girl.
你知道寶寶是女生
And you really do want her to be named Ruth.
你真的希望她叫蘿絲
Well, I'm not falling for that! Okay? Ruth is off the table!
我才不會上當 好吧？我們不考慮蘿絲
-But, Ross, you want the name Ruth. -Not like this!
-但羅斯，你要蘿絲這個名字 -現在我不要了
-嗨 -嗨
What's up?
怎麼了？
-Joey, I know. -What?
-喬伊，我知道了 -什麼？
-I know. -What?
-我知道了 -什麼？
-I know about your feelings. -Oh, my God, you do?
-我瞭解你的感覺 -天啊，真的嗎？
I'm sorry. Things worked out for Chandler and Monica, but that's rare.
我很遺憾，雖然錢德跟摩妮卡成功了 但那是少之又少的例子
I know. And this is so much more complicated than it was for those guys.
我知道 這比他們的情況複雜多了
I mean, it's Rachel, for God's sakes.
我是說她是瑞秋，天啊
For God's sakes, it's Rachel!
天啊，是瑞秋
I know! She's not only my friend, she's my pregnant friend.
我知道，她不只是我的朋友 她是我的孕婦朋友
She's my pregnant friend who's Ross 'ex!
她是我的孕婦朋友 還是羅斯的前女友
Yeah, that's Rachel.
對，那就是瑞秋
Beat me over the head with it.
我真的被搞糊塗了
What am I gonna do? I keep trying to get rid of these feelings.
我該怎麼辦？ 我試著不去想這些事
I stayed up all last night and made a list of everything I don't like about her.
昨晚我整夜沒睡 試著寫出我不喜歡她的地方
-You wanna hear it? -Yeah.
-你想聽聽看嗎？ -好
"She made me switch to light mayo." That's it! That's all I got!
「她要我改吃低卡美乃滋」 就那樣，我只想到那個
You know what? Tastes the same and my pants fit better.
你知道嗎？味道一樣 但我的褲子松多了
Joey, I think you're getting upset for nothing. This is probably just a crush.
喬伊，我覺得你是庸人自擾 或許你只是被愛情沖昏了頭
You think?
你真的那麼認為？
Absolutely. You get this rush of feelings, but then it goes away.
當然，你只是一時昏了頭 但那種感覺會消失的
Yeah, just a crush. That's all this is. It's a crush!
對，我只是沖昏了頭 沒錯，我只是沖昏了頭
I'm Joey. I don't get deep feelings.
我是喬伊，我不會玩真的
There you go. Crushes happen all the time.
好了 人常會被沖昏了頭
I know I've had them for all you guys. Except for Ross and Chandler.
我對你們這些男生也會有那種感覺 羅斯跟錢德除外
-And I'm sure you've had them for us. -Not really.
-我相信你對我們也是 -不盡然
Throw me a bone here.
丟根骨頭給我
So I called the doctor.
我打電話給醫生了
-Now we both know the sex of the baby. -What?
-現在我們都知道寶寶的性別 -什麼？
That's right. The student has become the master.
沒錯 我是青出於藍勝於藍
-Ross, I swear. I don't know. -Oh, come on, you know it's a girl.
-羅斯，我發誓我真的不知道 -少來了，你知道寶寶是女孩
A what?
什麼？
You really didn't know?
你真的不知道？
-We're having a girl? -No.
-我們要有個女兒了？ -不
-That's what you said. -No.
-你是那麼說的 -不
-You said girl. -Yes. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
-你說它是女孩 -對，我真的很抱歉
I'm not! We're having a girl!
沒關係，我們要有個女兒了
Sometimes I can't believe it's with you, but still, we're having a girl!
有時候我不敢相信孩子的爸是你 但我們要有個女兒了
I know! You know what? I'm putting Ruth back on the table.
我知道，你知道嗎？ 我要重新考慮蘿絲這個名字
Yes, we'll have ourselves a little baby Ruth.
對，我們要生下小蘿絲了
-Permission to veto. -Yes, please.
-請求否決 -好吧，否決
Do I smell essential oils?
這是精油味嗎？
Yeah. I'm gonna take a bath. I was just gonna get a magazine.
對，我要去洗澡 我想拿本雜誌
What do you think you're doing?
你覺得你在做什麼？
Leaving my troubles behind?
忘了我的麻煩？
I know that you're new at this, but this is unacceptable bath decorum.
我知道你是新手 但這不合乎洗澡的禮儀
It's so hard to care when you're this relaxed.
看到你這麼輕鬆 我真的很難挑剔
Okay, fine. You can have the bath, but I am taking your boat.
好吧，你可以洗澡 但我要拿走你的船
Now you're just a girl in a tub.
現在你是愛洗澡的女生
Hi, bubbles. Manly.
嗨，泡泡澡，太有男子氣概了
I thought I would drop by and let you know how it went.
我想順道過來 告訴你結果
You told her?
你跟她說了？
She pulled it out of me! She's like a conversational wizard!
是她套我的 她真的很會逼別人
-How did it go? -You were wrong. He doesn't like me.
-結果如何？ -你錯了，他不喜歡我
How would you like it if I sent you to Lee Majors' house..
你會有什麼感覺 如果我把你送到李梅傑的家
and I told you he liked you and you went there..
我告訴你他喜歡你 你跑進去…
and you found out that he didn't like you. How would you feel?
發現他並不喜歡你 你會有什麼感覺？
-I don't think I'd care. -Really? Lee Majors is hot.
-我想我不會在乎 -真的嗎？李梅傑很性感
-Hello? -We're in the bathroom!
-哈囉 -我們在浴室裡
-Why? -Because it's a relaxing and enjoyable time!
-為什麼？ -因為它既輕鬆又有趣
-What are you guys doing in here? -Oh, my God.
-你們在這裡做什麼？ -天啊
A friend he's looking at differently, but it's wrong.
他對一個朋友的感覺不一樣 但那是不對的
-It's Rachel! -You like Rachel?
-是瑞秋 -你喜歡瑞秋？
It's no big deal. Phoebe and I talked. It's a crush. It'll go away.
那沒什麼了不起的，菲比跟我談過 我只是沖昏了頭，我會清醒過來的
Dude, you gotta rearrange your bubbles.
你得重新排列 泡泡的位置
Mazel tov.
恭喜你
Ross and I were looking for you.
羅斯跟我在找你們
What are we all doing in here? Oh, my.
我們在這裡做什麼？天啊
-Honey, cover it up with the boat. -It's not an aircraft carrier.
-用船把它蓋起來 -它不是航空母艦
Hello?
哈囉
We're all in here, and we'd love for you to join us!
我們都在這裡 希望你能加入我們
Well, hey! What's going on? Oh, cool boat. Oh, no.
嘿，發生了什麼事？ 很酷的船，不
-Did you tell them? -No. I was waiting for you.
-你告訴他們了嗎？ -不，我在等你
-Tell us what? -We're having a girl.
-告訴我們什麼？ -我們懷的是女兒
Oh, wow! Really?
哇，真的嗎？
I'll get you later.
我待會再加入你們
All right. It's a new day. And it's just a crush.
好吧，這是全新的一天 我只是被沖昏了頭
That's all. Just a little crush.
沒錯，我沖昏了頭
All that worrying I was doing? That was crazy.
我到底在擔心什麼？ 那太瘋狂了
Like my friend the bird here would say, "It was cuckoo!"
我的小鳥朋友會說 「那跟瘋子一樣」
Everything's gonna be fine. It's just a crush.
一切都會沒事 我只是沖昏了頭
-Hi, sweetie. -I love you.
-嗨，甜心 -我愛你
It's nice to do this together, isn't it?
我們能一起這麼做 真的很棒吧？
Yeah. And what you're doing feels so good.
對，你讓我感覺很好
I'm not touching you.
我沒有碰你
-You're not? -It's the salts.
-是嗎？ -那是浴鹽
Oh, sweet Lord, new realms of pleasure.
天啊，那是感官新領域
Whatever keeps you off the balcony, big guy.
只要能讓你忘了陽台的事 就行了，大男人